costafarms.com 2018-11-22

# Privacy Policy | Costa Farms

**Our Commitment to Privacy and Security**  
Costa Farms recognizes the importance of maintaining your privacy and keeping your information secure. This policy describes how we collect, use, and safeguard the personal information you provide to us and should assist you in making informed decisions when using our site. 

**Why Do We Collect Information?**  
We collect information to allow us to enhance and personalize your experience on our Web site. 

**What Information Do We Collect?**   
When you visit our Web site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web site. 

**Personal Information You Choose to Provide**  
Email Information: If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. Web Site Use Information: Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology called "cookies" (see explanation below, "What Are Cookies?") and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site. This information is collected on an aggregate basis. None of this information is associated with you as an individual. Email Service Provider: Costa Farms uses an email service provider to send our promotional emails, newsletters, etc. to our subscriber list. The email addresses in this subscriber list are not sold, shared, or rented by Costa Farms or our provider. If you would like to be removed from our email list, click on the "unsubscribe" link when you receive such an offer or send us an email request at [information`@`costafarms.com](mailto:information@costafarms.com?subject=Costa%20Farms%20privacy%20policy). We do NOT sell, share, or rent telephone numbers or email addresses for third-party use. 

**How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?**  
Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing customer service, and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services, and special offers we think you will find valuable. The lists used to send you product and service offers are developed and managed under our traditional corporate standards designed to safeguard the security and privacy of our customers’ personal information. You can notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link when you receive such an offer or by sending us an email request at [information`@`costafarms.com](mailto:information@costafarms.com?subject=Costa%20Farms%20privacy%20policy). 

**What Are Cookies?**  
Cookies are a feature of Web browser software that allows Web servers to recognize the computer used to access a Web site. Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored by a user’s Web browser on the user’s hard drive. Cookies can remember what information a user accesses on one Web page to simplify subsequent interactions with that Web site by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user’s transactions on related Web pages. This makes it easier for a user to move from Web page to Web page and to complete commercial transactions over the Internet. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized. 

**How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?**  
We use Web site browser software tools such as cookies and Web server logs to gather information about our Web site users’ browsing activities, in order to constantly improve our Web site and better serve our customers. This information assists us to design and arrange our Web pages in the most user-friendly manner and to continually improve our Web site to better meet the needs of our customers and prospective customers. Cookies help us collect important business and technical statistics. The information in the cookies lets us trace the paths followed by users to our Web site as they move from one page to another. Web server logs allow us to count how many people visit our Web site and evaluate our Web site’s visitor capacity. We do not use these technologies to capture your individual email address or any personally identifying information about you. 

**Sharing Information with Strategic Partners**  
We may enter into strategic marketing alliances or partnerships with third parties who may be given access to personal information including your name and address for the purpose of providing you information regarding products and services that we think will be of interest to you. We do NOT sell, share, or rent telephone numbers or email addresses for third party use. In connection with strategic marketing alliances or partnerships,we will retain all ownership rights to the information, and we will not share information regarding your social security number or other personal financial data. You can notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by sending us an email request at [information`@`costafarms.com](mailto:information@costafarms.com?subject=Costa%20Farms%20privacy%20policy)

**How Do We Protect Your Information?**  
Information Security: We utilize encryption/security software to safeguard the confidentiality of personal information we collect from unauthorized access or disclosure and accidental loss, alteration, or destruction. Valuation of Information Protection Practices: Periodically, our operations and business practices are reviewed for compliance with corporate policies and procedures governing the security, confidentiality, and quality of our information. Employee Access, Training, and Expectations: Our corporate values, ethical standards, policies and practices are committed to the protection of customer information. In general, our business practices limit employee access to confidential information, and limit the use and disclosure of such information to authorized persons, processes and transactions. 

**How Can You Access and Correct Your Information?**  
You may request access to all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain in our database by emailing [information`@`costafarms.com](mailto:information@costafarms.com?subject=Costa%20Farms%20privacy%20policy). 

**Do We Disclose Information to Outside Parties?**  
We may provide aggregate information about our customers, sales, Web site traffic patterns, and related Web site information to our affiliates or reputable third parties, but this information will not include personally identifying data, except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy. 

**What About Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information?**  
We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights. 

**What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?**  
We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Web site. Please review the Privacy Policy of the linked Web site for further information.
